sunburnswimwear.com.au 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | Sunburn Swimwear

Sunburn values your privacy.

## Privacy & Use of Information.

**What we use your personal information for**  
Sunburn keeps confidential all personally identifiable information you provide us. If you register your details with us, or order a catalogue, your information allows us to communicate with you about our products, promotions and activities. The information that you provide us through our website will be used to update our customer database. This information is for Sunburn's internal use only, and is used for the purpose of customer communication. If you purchase any of your products online, we will also use the information you provide us to process your order and its delivery to you.

**Accessing your information**  
We like to know that the personal information you provide us is accurate, complete and up to date. If you notice that your personal information is missing or incorrect, you can update your details online on our website. So that we can continue to offer you great offers and promotion info, we give you the opportunity to say yes to being contacted by Sunburn by email. This is totally your choice and you can opt out of the future contact whenever you want. If you would like your name deleted from the database please email enquiries@sunburn.com.au requesting deletion. You will be deleted from our database within 48 hours.

**Sharing information with third parties**  
We promise that when you provide us with personal information, it will only be used by Sunburn. We will not share the information third parties except to disclose:

  * your name (and possibly your suburb) if you win a Sunburn competition; or
  * your name and postal address to organisations that assist us with customer communications (to be used solely for that purpose).

**Deleting information**  
We ensure that any personal information we no longer need is either destroyed or that you become permanently unidentifiable from the information,

**Cardholder account data**  
Sunburn does not store any cardholder data, all credit card payment services are secure and are handled by SecurePay.

**SecurePay Security Standards**  
We prioritise protecting your personal and order information and have created a secure online shopping environment . The focus of our security is centred around the safe processing and storage of sensitive personal Credit Card, Charge Card and Direct Entry information. PCI DSS (Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard) Compliance is a strict security standard the card schemes (Visa and MasterCard) have introduced globally to ensure personal information is properly protected. SecurePay holds the highest level of PCI DSS accreditation.

**Vecta Corporation**  
SecurePay’s Operations Network is audited on an ongoing basis by external auditors, namely Vectra Corporation, for the purpose of certifying compliance with PCI DSS. Ongoing network scans, a requirement of PCI DSS, are completed regularly and are performed by McAfee Secure.

The services that SecurePay is authorised to provide under PCI DSS include:

  * Authorisation Services
  * Clearing / Settlement Services
  * IPSP (e-Commerce)
  * Payment Gateway
  * Switch
  * Processing MOTO Transations
  * 3-D Secure Access Control Server

Please see [www.securepay.com.au/security_standards.html](http://www.securepay.com.au/security_standards.html) for more information.

**The nature of our business.**  
We are principally a retailer. Retailing can utilise a number of facilities and functions including shops (off the street and in shopping centres), the Internet, promotional material (using various forms including paper and electronic mail outs), credit and other card systems, lay by arrangements and reward schemes. As a successful and long established retailer we carry out any or all of these means of business from time to time.

**Copyright**  
Sunburn asserts copyright and all other intellectual rights in relation to the content of this Internet site and code used to create it, unless stated otherwise  
Sunburn also reserves copyright and all other intellectual property rights in relation to all of its documents and images appearing on or linked to this web site. Users of this website may download a single copy of these documents or images for their personal use only.

**Contact us**  
For further information on Sunburn, or if you have any questions about the personal information we hold about you, why we hold it and how we use and disclose your information, please email [enquiries@sunburn.com.au](mailto:enquiries@sunburn.com.au) or call +61 2 8339 8222.

More information on privacy legislation is available from the Federal Privacy Commissioner at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/)
